<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="descr126281"><![CDATA[Snakelike body\n\n
Undershot mouth.\n\n
Dorsal (back) and anal fins are fused with the tail fin forming a single ribbon running along much of the body.]]></string>
    <string name="descr151353"><![CDATA[The body shows a number of dark vertical bands\n\n
Two back fins that are clearly separate.\n\n
A black spot can be seen in the back end of the frontal back fin.]]></string>
    <string name="descr154281"><![CDATA[A high backed body, flattened at the sides.\n\n
The diameter of the eye is smaller than the distance between eye and mouth.\n\n
Slightly undershot mouth that can be extended]]></string>
    <string name="descr154333"><![CDATA[Mouth positioned straight at end\n\n
The eye has a red spot in the upper half\n\n
Front of the back fin and bellyfin are positioned in line.]]></string>
    <string name="descr236462"><![CDATA[2-4 spines are positioned in front of the back fin.\n\n
Back and anal fin are postioned at the back of the body.\n\n
Males in the breeding season have a red throat and belly and blue eyes.]]></string>
    <string name="descr126915"><![CDATA[Big, broad head with swollen cheeks and lips. Undershot mouth.\n\n
Belly fins have merged into a sucker.\n\n
Red and brown marble pattern on body and head.]]></string>
    <string name="descr154373"><![CDATA[6 short barbels at the mouth, 4 on the upper lip and 2 in the corners of the mouth.\n\n
The sides show a line of dark brown spots\n\n
there is a forked spike below the eye that is oriented towards the tail.]]></string>
    <string name="descr154388"><![CDATA[One barbel on the chin\n\n
2 back fins that are clearly separate\n\n
Belly fins are located in front of the breast fins]]></string>
    <string name="descr126933"><![CDATA[The eyes are positioned high in the head\n\n
The nostrils are short tubes\n\n
Two separate back fins, of which the hindmost one is fused with the tail fin ]]></string>
    <string name="descr126913"><![CDATA[The eyes are positioned high in the head\n\n
The hindmost back fin and the anal fin slope to the back\n\n
The fish had a pale colour, light blue gray at the sides with fuzzy dark spots]]></string>
    <string name="descr151302"><![CDATA[The smallest perch like fish, up to 14cm\n\n
The body, tail and back fin has tiny dark spots\n\n
Bottom dweller with a preference for deeper water]]></string>
    <string name="descr127196"><![CDATA[The two back fins touch, the hindmost being longer that the front one\n\n
The operculum (gill) has upright spikes\n\n
No scales on the thead]]></string>
    <string name="descr154165"><![CDATA[Undershot mouth\n\n
The front of the back fin is positioned clearly behind the front of the belly fins\n\n
Bright red fins]]></string>
    <string name="descr154210"><![CDATA[Anal fin and back fin are positioned near the back of the body\n\n
The head sports a flat and broad mouth\n\n
The body has golden dots or stripes]]></string>
    <string name="descr151308"><![CDATA[The two back fins are separate\n\n
The upper jaw extends to behind the eye\n\n
The operculum (gill) is pointy]]></string>
    <string name="descr126507"><![CDATA[In front of the back fin are 9 to 11 spikes\n\n
The belly fin is silver\n\n
Anal fin and back fin are positioned near the back of the body]]></string>
    <string name="descr154343"><![CDATA[The iris of the eye is orange\n\n
The fins are round in shape\n\n
The mouth has a small barbel at each corner]]></string>
    <string name="descr151290"><![CDATA[The operculum (gill) often has an dark orange spot, surrounded with a black rim\n\n
The back fin has a front part with tough spikes and a higher back part\n\n
The body has a prominent pattern with blueish sides and yellowbrown and red spots]]></string>
    <string name="descr126916"><![CDATA[The front back fin has a black spot in the back\n\n
The belly fins are grown together into a sucker\n\n
The hindmost back fin is straight]]></string>
</resources>
