<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name"><![CDATA[BOWL NL sweet Leiden]]></string>
    <string name="project_name"><![CDATA[Blik Onderwater in Leiden (BOWL)]]></string>
    <string name="mail_body"><![CDATA[Sent from the iMarineLIfe App (NL Sweet BOWL Leiden)]]></string>
    <string name="mail_to"><![CDATA[info@imarinelife.com, nielsschrieken@gmail.com,bowl.waarnemingen@gmail.com,visreservaatleiden@gmail.com]]></string>
    <string name="mail_from"><![CDATA[mailer.imarinelife@gmail.com]]></string>
    <string name="mail_from_password"><![CDATA[D41k@ppj3]]></string>
    <string name="language"><![CDATA[en]]></string>
    <string name="catalog_name"><![CDATA[BOWL]]></string>
    <string name="expansionfile_main_version"><![CDATA[0]]></string>
    <string name="expansionfile_patch_version"><![CDATA[0]]></string>
    <string name="introduction"><![CDATA[The project \'Blik Onder Water Leiden\' brings the under water life of the Leiden canals under the attention of the public.\n\n\n\n
iMarineLife supports BOWL with the \'NL Sweet IBOWL Leiden\' app that helps to recognize the fish that are present in the Leiden canals. This enthuses tourists and residents alike. \n\n\n\n
The app supports residents with documenting and presenting their findings in the Leiden canals. If snorkeldives are performed they are done under professional guidance.]]></string>
    <string name="help_for_observations"><![CDATA[Specify for each species in the fieldguide if you did \n\n\n
   \t0\t\t- not \n\n\n
   \t<11\t\t- rarely (up to 10)\n\n\n
   \t<51\t\t- regularly (up to 50)\n\n\n
   \t>501\t- massively (more than 50)\n\n\n
see any individuals\n\n\n\n
Do not worry if you don\'t know if you saw or recognized the species. Then use 0\n\n\n
It is very likely that you may spot a species that is not on the list. Please send a photo to  visreservaatleiden@gmail.com.]]></string>
    <string name="thanks"><![CDATA[This version of the iMarineLife app was created with the cooperation of enthousiastic volunteers.\n\n\n
We thank the following people for:\n\n\n
- donating photographs: Aaf Verkade, Silvia Waajen, Jef Driesen, Ellen Kop, Erik van Vessem, Berhold Raadsen en Wijnand Vlierhuis.\n\n
- writing teksts: Aaf Verkade and Niels Schrieken\n\n
- building the app for Android: Marjon Roodzant\n\n
- and the initiators: Aaf Verkade and Niels Schrieken. \n\n\n
Aaf Verkade: www.blikonderwaterinleiden.nl\n\n
Niels Schrieken: www.biorganized.com\n\n\n
Finally we would like to thank everyone for using iMarineLife\n\n
and sending any sightings.]]></string>
</resources>
